&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：如果函数已使用BIND绑定
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If function is already bound using bind
以后可以反弹到不同的对象。
can be rebound to a different object later.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，在我们这个单元之前的讨论中，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, so in our this discussion a bit earlier in this unit,
我们谈到了一个尚未绑定的函数，
we talked about the idea that a function that is not yet bound,
你可以调用它的绑定并产生一个所谓的硬绑定函数，好吗？
you can call that bind on it and produces a so called hardbound function, all right?
该硬绑定函数固定到您说要将其绑定到的上下文，
That hardbound function is fixed to the context that you said to bind it to,
只有一种可能的方法来覆盖该绑定。
and there's only one possible way to override that binding.
您不能再次调用.bind，但是
You cannot call .bind on it again, but
您可以使用新的关键字调用它，这将产生以下效果
you could invoke it with a new key word, which would have the effect of
将其此行为覆盖为新构造的对象。
overriding its this behavior to be a newly constructed object.
所以这个问题的答案只能通过new关键字。
So the answer to that question is only via the new keyword.
你不能在其他地方调用.绑定和重新绑定它。
You cannot recall.bind and rebind it somewhere else.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：如果在箭头函数中定义变量，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If you define a variable inside an arrow function,
变量的作用域是箭头函数还是父作用域？
is that variable scoped to the arrow function or to the parent scope?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Good question.
箭头函数确实有词法作用域。
Arrow functions do have lexical scope.
他们只是没有这个关键字。
They just don't have this keyword.
我见过很多地方人们说
I've seen actually a number of places where people say
箭头函数没有作用域。
that arrow functions don't have scope.
他们绝对有范围。
They absolutely have scope.
它们是词法的，就像任何其他函数一样。
They are lexical just like any other function.
因此，如果在箭头函数中定义变量，则与定义
So if you define a variable inside of an arrow function it's exactly like defining
任何其他类型的函数中的任何其他变量。
any other variable in any other kind of function.
这两者之间唯一的区别，真的，就是常规的区别
The only difference between those two, really, is the difference of regular
函数定义this关键字，箭头函数不定义this关键字。
functions define a this keyword, and arrow functions don't define a this keyword.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：在this was回调的情况下，这个值是否取决于
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: In the case of the this were callback, does the value of this depend
关于高阶函数如何调用回调？
upon how the higher order function calls the callback?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，呼叫地点是唯一重要的事情。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes, the call site is the only thing that matters.
因此，如果您将函数传递到例如.map中，
So if you pass a function into say .map,
map如何调用回调是决定其this绑定的唯一因素。
how .map invokes your callback is the only thing that determines its this binding.
除非传入了硬绑定函数，在这种情况下，
Unless you have passed in a hardbound function, in which case,
您的硬绑定优先。
your hard binding has taking precedence.
但是.map内部，
But .map internally,
你可以把它想象成调用cb，打开，闭合的圆括号，或者类似的东西。
you can think of it as calling CB open closed parentheses or something like that.
那个调用站点没有绑定这个。
That call site isn't binding of this.
所以，是的，绝对是你的高阶函数，你的array.map或过滤器，
So yes, absolutely your high order functions, your array.map or filter,
所有那些绝对都有这种细微差别或怪癖，
all those, those all absolutely have this nuance or this quirk to it that
它们如何调用您的函数完全决定了这个上下文将是什么。
how they invoke your function entirely determines what the this context will be.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：当您设置Dunder Proto时会发生什么？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: What happens when you set dunder proto?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Good question.
对于您来说，使用Dunder Proto作为setter并不常见。
It is not very common for you to use the Dunder Proto as a setter.
从技术上讲，它既是一种获得者，也是一种设定者。
It is technically both a getter and a setter.
它几乎总是被用来引用它。
It is almost always used just to reference it.
我会说一般说来，
And I would say generally speaking,
这是一种重新连接对象原型链的反模式。
it's sort of an anti-pattern to rewire the prototype chain of an object.
但在ES6中，Dunder Proto也是正式的东西
But as of ES6, dunder proto is officially also something
它可以设置从一个对象到另一个对象的原型链接。
that can set the proto linkage from one object to a different object.
所以如果你有一个链接在这里的对象A
So if you have an object A that's linked over here and
然后你决定，我想把这个物体原型链接到这里，
then later you decide, I want that object prototype linked over here,
您可以使用Dunder proto作为设置器来更改它。
you can use dunder proto as a setter to change it.
还有一个实用程序
And there's also a utility or
称为object.setPrototypeOf的API版本。
an API version of that called object.setPrototypeOf.
这将允许你拿起任何物体并重新布线。
Which will allow you to take any any object and rewire it.
我想说，0.001%的情况下，你有没有看到有人重新接线
I would say 0.001% of the time do you ever see anybody rewiring
原型链，但是是的，你绝对可以做它们
prototype chains, but yes, you absolutely can do them and
在某些情况下，它实际上可能非常强大和有用。
it might in fact be very powerful and useful in certain circumstances.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：做原型对象，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Do the prototype objects,
每个功能都预装了方块？
the squares come pre-installed with every function?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以问题是。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So the question is.
在我正在绘制的图表中，我们为一个函数画了一个圆。
In the diagram that I was drawing, where we drew a circle for a function.
然后我们在这里画了一个正方形，这是它的点原型。
And then we drew a square over here, which was its dot prototype.
常规函数有点原型，箭头函数没有。
Regular functions have dot prototypes, arrow functions do not.
所以如果我们有一个正则函数，它是一个声明，它是一个表达式，
So if we have a regular function, it's a declaration, it's an expression,
它是匿名的，它的名字。
it's anonymous, its name.
所有这些都会有一个正方形。
All of those are always gonna have a square.
但是如果你做一个箭头函数它就不会有原型了，
But if you make an arrow function it's not gonna have a prototype,
这就是为什么当你对它调用new时，它失败了。
which is why by the way when you call new on it, it fails.
因为它不是构造函数。
Because it is not a constructor.
它没有原型，所以不能用new关键字构造它。
It doesn't have a prototype so it can't be constructed with the new keyword.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：这只是一个附带问题，因为你说要使用关键字
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It just a side question because you said use the keyword
也是超级的。
super also.
它也可以用作原型吗？
Can it be used as a prototype too?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Good question.
所以超级关键字，能够在类之外使用，
So the super keyword, is able to used outside of classes,
当你处理对象和它们的方法时。
when you're dealing with objects and their methods.
所以你可以去拿一个物体
So you could go and take one object and
使用原型链接将其连接到另一个对象。
wire it up to another object with the prototype linkage.
我们会稍稍看一下这个模式。
We're gonna look at that pattern in a bit.
制作没有类链接的对象的想法。
The idea of making objects that are linked without classes.
从技术上讲，你可以在这些方法中使用一个超级来
And you could use technically a super inside one of those methods to
参考原型链的一些东西。
refer to something of the prototype chain.
警告是超级关键字不是动态绑定的，
The caveat is that the super keyword is not dynamically bound,
它是静态绑定的，这意味着您实际上必须创建一个对象
it is statically bound which means to use that you actually have to create an object
与其中的方法一起使用literal，并且必须在此时将其链接到对象。
literal with the method in it, and it has to at that moment be linked to the object.
所以换句话说，你不能拿一个物体，改变它的原型，然后
So in other words, you won't be able to take one object, change its prototype, and
神奇地有超级参考另一个。
magically have super refer to the other one.
它在第一次创建时被静态绑定到任何链接的地方。
It is statically bound the first time it's created to wherever it's linked.
但是，是的，您可以在Object文字内部使用超级
But yes, you can use super inside of object literals
只要它们是简明的方法形式。
as long as they are the concise method form.